Welcome back.
欢迎回来
Now it's time to start making some figures.
现在开始绘制一些图表
In this lesson, I'll teach you how to use software called Tableau
在这节课 我将指导你如何使用软件 Tableau
to create your visualizations.
创建可视化图表
Tableau makes it simple to import data from Excel, a text file, a database and
Tableau 使你能够轻松地从 Excel、文本文件、数据库以及其他来源中导入数据
Then you can easily build interactive dashboards.
然后就可以轻松地创建交互式仪表板
Unlike software such as matplotlib or
与 matplotlib 或 D3 等软件不同
d3, you don't need to know how to program to make awesome plots.
你不需要了解编程就能构建很酷的图表
First, let's hear more from a Tableau pro.
首先 来听听 Tableau 达人的介绍
&gt;&gt; Hi, I'm here with Trina Chiasson, she is a product manager at Tableau.
坐在我身边的是 Trina Chiasson 她是 Tableau 的产品经理
And today she's going to talk to us about Tableau and give us some demos.
今天她将向我们介绍 Tableau 并做一些演示
So, first, before we start,
在开始前
can you tell us a little bit about your experience at Tableau?
能介绍下你在 Tableau 的经历吗?
&gt;&gt; Sure, and thanks for having me.
— 当然 谢谢你的邀请
I've been with Tableau for about a year now,
我在 Tableau 已经有一年时间了
just over a year, and I'm a product manager with Tableau.
刚刚超过一年 是一名产品经理
I focus on innovation at the company, which means that I get to work with
我的工作是进行创新
a lot of different people across the organization.
需要与公司内各个部门的同事合作
And I came to Tableau from a data analysis background, as well.
我来 Tableau 之前就已经拥有数据分析经验
&gt;&gt; Awesome, cool, so Tableau is software for creating data visualizations.
— 很棒 Tableau 是用来创建数据可视化的软件
So say I already have my data in Excel, and I can make visualizations in Excel,
假设我已经将数据放在了 Excel 中 我可以在 Excel 中进行可视化
so what is it about Tableau that is better than Excel?
Tableau 比 Excel 好在哪呢?
Why do I want to use Tableau?
我为何要使用 Tableau?
&gt;&gt; Yeah, that's a great question.
— 问得好
Excel is an amazing product, it's been around for a very long time.
Excel 是一款很棒的产品 已经有很多年的发展历史了
Actually, it first hit the market, the first version, in 1985.
实际上第一版面世于 1985 年
So it's kind of hard for
所以我们很难想象
us to collectively remember what data analysis was like 30 years ago.
30 年前数据分析是什么样的状况
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
— 是的
&gt;&gt; But it's come a long way since then, and
— 但是到现在已经很多年了
Excel has improved dramatically, too.
Excel 有了非常大的改进
But Excel is fundamentally designed as a spreadsheet application for
但是 Excel 本质上是个电子表格应用
holding your data and doing advanced calculations.
用于存储数据和进行高级计算
Tableau is designed as an exploratory tool, a way to quickly see and
Tableau 则被设计为一种探索工具 可以使我们快速地查看、
understand your data, and do analysis and really move things around,
理解数据并进行分析 到处移动各个部分
change things, iterate and ask deep questions of your data
更改内容 进行迭代 对数据提出深层问题